National Negro Opera Company Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1934-1970, (193 folders) (Box 7-12)
  - Calloway, Susie, 1961 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Cambell, Robert, 1950 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Campbell, Byron, 1954 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Campbell, Dick (Dick Campbell Concerts, Inc. Artists Management), 1945-1956, Mr. Campbell was the husband and agent for Muriel Rahn. (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Campfield, Marion, 1954 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Canada Dry Corporation (F. A. Nerret), 1960 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Capitol Cab Association (Calvin Reid, Manager), 1958 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Capitol Furs (Norman Silverman), 1962 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Capitol Transit Company (Washington, D.C.), 1947-1951 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Cardwell, Elizabeth, 1937, Elizabeth Cardwell was mary Cardwell Dawson's mother. (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Cardwell, Harold V., 1948, 1958, Harold V. Cardwell was Mary Cardwell Dawson's brother. (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carmena, Zelna, 1961 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carnegie, Amos H., 1950 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carnegie Hall (New York), 1951 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carnegie Music Hall (Pittsburgh), 1947, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carr, A. D., 1947, 1951 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carr, Irene, 1944 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carraway, Gertrude, 1953 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Carrington, Rita Maria, 1955-1961 see also Notebooks: Stenographer's notebook. Notebook belonging to Rita Carrington see also Photographs: Carrington, Rita Maria (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Carter, Horace, 1957 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Carter, Jesse M., 1959 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Carter-Moses, Helen, 1948 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Cash, M. L., Mrs., 1953 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Cassell, A. I. (A. I. Cassell Land Corporation), 1960 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Cato, Minto Alberta, 1918-1955 see also Photographs: Cato, Minto (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Cavin, Patty, 1955 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Cayton, Horace, 1943 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Center Market City Managers Office (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Central Opera Service (New York), 1956-1961 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Centre Studio (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Century Club, Washington, D.C. (Meta Mounsey, President), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Ceylon. Embassy. (Aziz Ahmed, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Ceylon. Embassy. (R. S. Gunewardene, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chamberlin, John D., 1950-1961 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chapman, Ewell & Benton Law Office (Washington, D.C.), 1959, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Charner, Leo (Charner Motor Company, Washington, D.C.), 1952 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chase and Sanborn Coffee (Public Relations, Washington, D.C.), 1960 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Cherry, Robert T. and Mrs., 1952-1953 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chevrolet Company (Pittsburgh Office), 1954 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - The Chicago Bee (Olive Diggs, Editor), 1943 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chicago Defender. (Metz L. P. Lochard, Editor in Chief; John H. Sengstacke, Publisher and Editor; David Kellum, City Editor), 1943-1944, 1953, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chicago Flexible Shaft Company, 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chicago Musical College, 1952 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chicago Sun Times (Marshall Field, Jr., Editor and Publisher; Irving Kupcinet), 1952, 1954, 1957 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chicago Tribune (Philip Maxwell), 1954, 1957 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chicago Urban League, 1952 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Childs, Mildred B., 1957 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chile. Embassy. (Walter Muller, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - China. Embassy. (Hollington K. Tong, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chinn, Eva, (Mrs. Crulan), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Chris Flower Shop, Washington, D.C. (Walter L. Christian), 1960 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Christian Heurich Brewing Company (Washington, D.C.), 1952 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Christian Science Monitor. (Harold Rogers, Music Critic), 1956 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Citizens Sponsoring Committee, 1951 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Clark, Marguerite B., 1957 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - The Cleveland News, 1955 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Clinkscales, William, 1944 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Club Ebony, New York. (Floyd Snelson - Public Relations), 1948 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Coca-Cola Bottling Company of Pittsburgh, 1954 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Coca-Cola Company, 1944, 1959 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Cohen, Alexander H., 1955 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Coleman, E. Marie, 1954, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Coleman, John, 1952 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Coleman, Ted, 1954 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Coles, Rubye M., 1957 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Collie, Harriet, undated, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Columbia Artists Management, Inc., New York (Ada G. Cooper, Booking Director; F. C. Schang, President; Kurt Winholdt; Leverett Wright), 1952-1953, 1955 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1955 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Columbia Concerts (New York), 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Columbia University (New York). Columbia Daily Spector, 1961 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Conley, Nubian J., 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Consolidated Feature Service, New York (Maurice Barron, Music Editor), 1951 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Continental Illinois Bank & Trust Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cook, Ann, 1943 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cook, Mrs. Clarence, 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cook, Destalear, 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cooper, Ester I., 1960 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Copeland, Nathan, 1945 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Corn Products Refining Company, Argo, Illinois. (Marguerite Sullivan), 1944 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cosmo Card Club (Pittsburgh), 1940 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cosmopolitan Community Church (Chicago), 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Costa Rica. Embassy. (Don Gonzalo J. Facio, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Costello, Paul, 1944 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Costlay, Marie, 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cotton, Pearl Smith, 1961 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - County Commissioners Office (Pittsburgh), 1938 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Crawford, A. D., 1945 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Crawford, Cheryl, 1955 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Crawford Grill (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Crawley, John, 1958 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Credit Association of Western Pennsylvania, 1946 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - The Crisis Magazine, Johnson Publications, New York (Roy Wilkins), 1944 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Crosthwait, Olive H., 1952 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Crusty Pie Company (Washington, D.C.), 1960 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cuba. Embassy. (Don Nicolas Arroyo, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Curtis, J. S., 1960, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Cutcher, B. S., undated, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Dabney, Edna, 1961 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - The Daily Worker. (Bob Reid, Theatrical Editor), 1944 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Dalton, Mattie, 1951 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Dandridge, Dorothy, 1955 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Dart Drug Corporation (Washington, D.C.), 1960 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Davidson, T. Douglas, 1953 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Davis, Alston A., 1950-1961 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Davis, Arthur, Mrs., 1954 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, Claire, 1944-1955 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, Florence, 1949 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, John W., 1956 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, Louise, 1944 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, Meyer, 1955 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, Minnie, 1951 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Davis, Ruby S., 1957-1960 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Dawson, Clarence, 1943-1961 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Dawson, Madero (?), 1956 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Dawson, Walter M. "Bob", 1943-1970, Walter M. Dawson was Mary Cardwell Dawson's husband. (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Dawson, William L. (U.S. Congressman, Illinois), 1954, 1957 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Daye, Elaine, 1952 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - De Paur, Leonard (DePaur's Infantry Chorus), 1955 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Dean Milk Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Dee, Mary, 1954 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority (Pittsburgh), 1950, 1953, 1956, 1960 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Democratic Party, National Democratic Headquarters, Washington, D.C. (Paul Butler, Chairman; Katie Oluchheim, Vice-Chairman), 1959 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Des Verney, Bertha, undated (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Design Printing Service, Inc., Washington, D.C. (Eugene Collins), 1957 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Detroit Public Library, 1962, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Diamond, Issac, 1960 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Dickerson, Earl B., 1954-1957 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Dickerson, Spencer, Mrs., 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Dickson, Ulicious, 1970 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Diggs, A. G., 1948 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Dimitry, Frances B., 1956 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Disham, Lucille, 1948 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - District of Columbia Government. Department of licenses and Inspections, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - District of Columbia Government. Executive Office, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - District of Columbia Government. Municipal Court, (Judge Armond W. Scott), 1950 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - District of Columbia Government. National Guard Armory, 1949 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - District of Columbia Government. Recreation Department, 1955 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - District News, Washington, D.C. (Joseph Ottenstein, Owner), 1961 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Diton, Carl, 1944 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Dixon, Mrs., 1944 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Doby, Marjel, 1959 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Dominican Republic. Embassy. (Don Manuel A. De Moya, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Donahoe's (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Donahue & Coe, Inc. (Miss McKeown), 1944 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Dorsey, Mrs. George, 1944 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Douglas, Ethel, 1960 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Dozier, Frank, 1954 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Drake-Kapphan Piano Co. (Pittsburgh), 1943 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Drew, John (Law Offices of Lewis, Drew, Gregg and Price - Pittsburgh), 1954-1955, 1960 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Drivers' Chauffeurs' and Helpers' Local 639 (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Drug Fair (Arlington, Virginia), 1960 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Du Mont Television Network (New York), 1955 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Duncan, Annie, 1961 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Duncan, Todd, 1960 see also Photographs: Duncan, Todd (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Duncan, Vernon B., 1956, 1958 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Duquesne University, (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Durrah and Darden (Law Offices, Washington, D.C.), 1955 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - E. J. Cronin Company (Fund Raising Campaigns, New York), 1944 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Eastman, Philip (Business Manager, New York Performing Guild, NNOC), 1956 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Eberson, John, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Ebony Magazine (John H. Johnson, Editor and Publisher), 1958 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Echers, Stanley, 1944 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Eckles, Blanche, 1958 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Edge, Thomas, 1952 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Edmonson, James, 1948 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Edwards (Lee), Barbara, 1950 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Edwards, Eva, 1948, 1954 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Edwards, Henry C., 1951 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Edwards, Joseph A., 1953 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Elkan, Henri, 1956 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Entertainment Bureau of America, New York (John Pransky), 1949, 1952 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Ethiopia. Embassy. (Yilma Deressa, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evans, Delna, undated (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evans, Harold R., 1936 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evans, Joseph E., 1944 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evans, Mary, 1952 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evans, Roy, 1958 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evanti, Lillian, undated see also Music: Evanti, Lillian see also Photographs: Evanti, Lillian (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Evening Star-The Sunday Star, Washington, D.C. (Rudolf Kauffmann, II), 1962, Letter to Walter Dawson regarding the news story concerning the death of Mary Cardwell Dawson that had appeared in the newspaper's issue of March 20, 1962. (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Ewell, Robert W. (Ewell & Benton Law Offices, Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Eymon, E. B., Jr., 1951 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Fairbanks, Morse & Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fairchild, Mr., 1952 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fairfax, Charles W., 1943 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fairmont Heights, Maryland (Doswell E. Brooks, Mayor), 1960 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fall, Frederick, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Falls, Francis, 1961 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Father and Mother Divine, 1956 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Favor, Ellen, 1954 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Federal Works Agency. Work Projects Administration, Washington, D.C. (Leigh E. Ore, Chief, Radion Section), 1941 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Federated Hotel Waiters Union, Local 356 (Willis Thomas), 1952 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Federation of Malaya. Embassy. (Ismail bin Dato' Abdul Rahman, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Feldman, Samuel, 1949 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Ferebee, Dorothy B., 1954, 1959 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Feuer, Cy, 1955 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fields, Lulu, undated (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Figur, George L., 1956 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fillion, Ferdinand (Fillion Studios, Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fineberg, Herman, 1954 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fireman's Department Store (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - First African Baptist Church (Savannah, Georgia), 1952 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - First Federal Savings & Loan Association (Homestead, Pennsylvania), 1948 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - First Holy Star Psychic Science Church, Inc., New York (V. D. S. Armistead), 1947 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - First National Bank of Chicago, 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fisher, Reginald Franklyn, 1947, 1949 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fisk University. (A. Wilson, Department of Music), 1937, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fitch, Floyd, 1936 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fitzpatrick, George, 1944 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Fleming, Thelma, 1961 (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Florsheim Shoe Company (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Foote Brothers Gear & Machine Corporation (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Ford, Henry, Jr., 1952 (Box-folder 8/23)
  - Ford Foundation (New York), 1959 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Forman, Margaret, 1955 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Fort Pitt Brewing Company, 1945, 1954 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Foster, Mamie V., 1954 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Fouche, Ruth Allen, undated (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Fountain, Beatrice, 1952 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - France. Embassy. (Herve Alphand, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Francis, P. M., 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Francis, William G., 1958-1959 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Frank Parsons Paper Company, Inc., Washington, D.C. (H. N. Phillips, President), 1958 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Franklin, William, 1949-1950 see also Photographs: Franklin, William (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Frazier's Funeral Home (Washington, D.C.), 1958 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Freeland, Ruth, 1956 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Freeman, Peggy Pierce, 1956 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Freeman, Peggy S., 1954 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Frerichs, Lois F. (Mrs. Carl W. Frerichs), 1944 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Friedberg Management, New York (Mrs. Searchinger), 1956 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Friend, John Edward, 1956 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Fritz Schoults & Company (Theatrical and Masquerade Costumes), Chicago, 1946 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Frochlish, Willard H., 1947-1948 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Fulbright, James William (U.S. Senator, Arkansas), 1959 see also Photographs: Fulbright, James William (Box-folder 8/25)
  - G. Schirmer, Inc. New York, 1945, 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gaines, Mrs. Ozella B., 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gaines Funeral Home, Pittsburgh (John Terry), 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gale Agency, Inc., Artists' Representatives, New York (Frank R. Sands), 1951 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gallager, Mr., 1960 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gambrell Funeral Home, Pittsburgh (Seth S. Gambrell, Jr.), 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gardner, Mr. and Mrs. B., undated (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gardner, Catherine, 1954, Probably a letter written by Katherine Cardwell Gardner. (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gardner, Katherine Cardwell, 1958, Katherine Cardwell Gardner was a sister of Mary Cardwell Dawson. (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Garland, Jay O., Mrs., 1958 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gay Color-Tones, Brooklyn, New York. (Edna Gay, Directress), 1944 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gaynor, Harry, Mrs., 1952 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - General American Transportation Corporation (Chicago), 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/1)
  - General Baking Company (Washington, D.C.), 1960 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - General Services Administration, Washington, D.C. (William P. McDonald, Chief of Consession), 1953 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - George, Albert B., Mrs., 1941 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gerber-Weiss Agency (Roy Gerber), 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Ghana. Embassy. (D. A. Chapman, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Giaquinto, Paolo, 1944 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Giant Eagle Market (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Giant Food Department Stores (Washington, D.C.), 1952, 1956, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gibbs, L., 1962 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gibson, Frances, 1960 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gibson, Marion, Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Giles, Roscoe, 1952, 1957 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gilkey, Stanley, 1955 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gillen & Coulter Company - Funeral Directors (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gilmore, Margaret, 1962 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Gimbel, Bernard S., 1955 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Givens, Joseph W., 1954 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Glass, Clyde, 1958 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Globe Ticket Company (Philadelphia), 1943, 1956 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gmilath Chesed "Tifereth Jacob" Jerusalem, Palestine (New York), 1944 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Godfrey, Arthur, 1952, 1955 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Godman, Leroy H., 1936, 1941 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gold, Ruby Moses, 1954 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Goldberg, Bernard, 1960 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Golden & Golden, Counselors at Law (New York), undated, Letter has been torn, most text missing. (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Golding, Geneva, 1954 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gomez, Joyce, 1945 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Goodkind, Andria Larney, 1955 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Goodwin, Lila, 1960 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gordon, Benjamin, 1960 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gordon, Delbert, Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Gorton, Alfred, 1934, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Graham, Clementina, 1948 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Graham, Gladys, 1951 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Grand Lodge Convention Committee, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), 1958 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Graves, W. A., 1944, 1953 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Gray, Mary, 1936 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Gray, Mr., 1952 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Grayson, Darnella, 1959 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Grazzini, Sylvia, 1944 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company (Baltimore), 1958 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Greater New York Industrial Directory, Inc., 1957 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Greater Pittsburgh All Nations Independence Day Festival, undated, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Greater Pittsburgh Home Improvement League (Mansfield Sales, President), 1954 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Green, Wade H., Jr., 1945 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Green, Wendell E., 1952, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Greene, Ann Garnett, 1946-1962 and undated (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Greene, Evelyn, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Greene, Harold, 1951 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Greene, Isaac, 1951 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Greene, Josephine Evans, 1956 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Greene, Martha, 1956 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Greenidge, Lisle, 1949 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Greggory, Mary, 1961 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Gregory, Monroe, 1959 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Griffin, Janet, 1960 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Griffith, Clark, 1955 see also Correspondence: Washington American League Base Ball Club, Washington, D.C. see also Photographs: Music Festivals, Griffith Stadium, Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Grimmell Brothers, Detroit, Michigan (A. W. Witt, Credit Manager), 1954 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Grinnell, Lloyd, 1952 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Grinnill Brothers (Detroit), 1952 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Guinn, Thelma, 1960 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Guyden, Ralph, 1956 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Gwin, Huel Brooks, 1955 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - H. Samsom, Inc. Funeral Directors (Pittsburgh), 1954 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hack Inspector Office (Washington, D.C.), 1961 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Haggans, Merie J., 1946 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hailstock, Virginia Mae, 1941, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Haines, Margaret, 1936 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hairston, Jester, 1959 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Haiti. Embassy. (Ernest Bonhomme, Ambassador), 1959 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hall, Inez, Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hall, Woolsey, 1953, 1958 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hallman, David K., 1960 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hallman, Thomas, Mr. and Mrs., 1960 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Hamilton, Hazel, 1952 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Handy, Doris (President, Womens Committee, Pittsburgh), 1955 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1936, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Hansell, Charles J., 1957 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Hansen, Edna, 1943 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Harangue, Pansy H., 1940 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Hargraves, H. M., 1936, 1954 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Harper, Solomon, 1957 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Harris, Alfonzo B., 1949 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Harris, Bertha M., 1961 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Harris, Carrie A., 1952 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Harris, Ethel Ramos, 1936, 1948-1959 and undated see also Photographs: Harris, Ethel Ramos (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Harris, Holford, undated (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harris, W. A., Mr. and Mrs., 1938 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison, E. L., 1953 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison, E. W., 1950 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison, Jack, 1951 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison, Marie, 1959 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison, Pearlie Cox, 1954 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison, Sarah, 1957 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harrison's Cafe (Washington, D.C.), 1951 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Harvey, William J., Mrs., 1954 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Hawes, Mae, 1943, Incomplete draft letter. (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Hayes, Lola W., 1955 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Hayes, Nellie, 1960 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Hayes Printing Company (New York), 1944 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Haygood, W. C., Mrs., 1943 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Hayman, Coreania and Lillian, 1945 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Hays, A. L., 1944 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Haythorne, Peggy, 1961 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Hecht's Company, Washington, D.C. (Mr. Friberg - Public Relations Department), 1953 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Hedges, Janice, 1943 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Hedrick, La Ursa Snelson, 1954, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Height, Dorothy (President, National Council of Negro Women, Washington, D.C.), 1961 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Heighton, Wendell (Concert Artists Management, South Pasadena, California, 1939 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Heinz, Clifford S., Mrs., 1943, 1954 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Heller's Bakeries (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Henderson, Rev. Dr., undated (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Henry Fuel Company (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Hereford, Bernice, 1960 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Heury, Mamie, 1961 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Heydorn, Hugo R., 1944 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Highs' Dairy Products Corporation (Washington, D.C.), 1959 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hightower, Madeline, 1954, 1958 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hill, Bertha, 1948 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hill, Clara K., 1936 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hilyer, Amanda V. Gray, 1944 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hinds, ?, 1945, Contains no correspondence. (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hines, Laura, 1951 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hoffman, Isaac O., 1958 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Hoffman Beverages, 1951 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Holden, Peter G., 1956 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Holland, Beal L., 1954, 1958, 1961 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Holland, Jeanne, undated (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Holland-Forbes, Kathleen, 1941 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Holly, Sorer Margaret D., 1960 (Box-folder 9/17)